Ryosuke Hujisawa

Full-Stack Developer

interview@off.tokyo Vancouver, BC 236-668-4441

Personal Profile

I have been working for a Full-Stack Developer for 4 years, with my most recent experience being a web developer. My strong point is the "patient". I had a experienced working with a one company on a long-term basis. I want to long-term basis with you.

Work Experience - 1 (Intern)

Apple Corporation Ad inc

January 2014 - December 2015

Key Skills(iOS Developer)

Familiarity with Swift4, perfect(Server-side Swift), Realm, React Native, or any mobile app development. AdMob Mobile Ads Operation

Job Details

I experienced testing and management of iOS applications. And I learned iOS development through modification of Swift 3 code.

I got a chance to develop original apps from the boss. I independently developed an application called "Lupo Maker" and experienced release to the App Store and advertisement operation.

Work Experience - 2 (Full Time)

Apple Corporation Ad inc

January 2016 - March 2018

Key Skills(Web Developer)

Practical understanding of Javascript (ES6, Node.js), HTML5 and CSS, Bootstrap, AJAX, JQuery, and Experienced PHP MAMP and WordPress.

Experience deploying Applications to AWS, Heroku and experience with one or more database systems MySQL

Job Details

We have developed an in-house reception system with three development teams. We used Git for version control and chat work on API. I wrote the inside with JS and PHP.

We have developed the Internet shop with three development teams. We used Git for version control and developed an online payment system with Stripe. We selected AWS for the infrastructure environment.

I learned the importance of team development and the importance of communication with designers. What I am most proud of through this job is having the experience of implementing a wonderful external system "Stripe".

PERSONAL SIDE ROJECT

 $(2013 \sim 2018)$

Wordtranslate(Translation of sentences into words)

January 2013 - December 2014

· Bootstrap, PHP, AWS and Python

Wesound(Music material share like SoundCloud)

February 2015 - December 2017

· WordPress, HTML5 and CSS, JQuery, MySQL, PHP, AWS

Portfolio(My self-introduction site)

January 2018 - June 2018

· Bootstrap, GitHub

World Clock(Specify time and convert)

January 2018 - June 2018

Server-side Swift - Perfect, ubuntu, HTML5, CSS3

Education

 $(2012 \sim 2017)$

Horikoshi High School

March 2012- April 2015

· General high school, Science course major

Senshu University Faculty of Computer Science

(Night school for working adult student) March 2015 - April 2017

• A technology foundation of information and computation, Analysis and research of compiler structure, Basic programming with C language

Key Skills

(1997 ~ 2018)

Laugh often Love much Passion for work Dream Big Relationship Music is always